<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>VPNresellers blog</title>
    <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog</link>
    <description>We are the global number 1 VPN resell program.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:22:05 GMT</pubDate>
    <dc:date>2023-08-04T20:22:05Z</dc:date>
    <dc:language>en</dc:language>
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Whitelabel VPN integration</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/wordpress-whitelabel-vpn-integration</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our Wordrpess - Woocommerce Plugin guide for VPNresellers, in this guide I will go over step by step how to install and use the plugin. So that you can sell and deliver VPN to your customers automatically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our Wordrpess - Woocommerce Plugin guide for VPNresellers, in this guide I will go over step by step how to install and use the plugin. So that you can sell and deliver VPN to your customers automatically.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;h4&gt;1. Install Wordpress and Woocommerce&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;- First things first, is to install wordpress at your webhosting provider. If you do not have a webhost provider yet, get this first for example at&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href="https://www.hostgator.com/"&gt;Hostgator.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Once installed proceed to install Woocommerce which you can download on their website &lt;a href="https://woocommerce.com/"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Because we offer VPN subscriptions, it is mandetory to get Woocommerce Subscriptions plugin, download it &lt;a href="https://woocommerce.com/products/woocommerce-subscriptions/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;2. Install the VPNresellsers plugin&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;- Download the VPNresellers plugin &lt;a href="https://vpnclient.app/modules/woocommerce.zip"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Login into your wordpress site, click on "Plugins" and then "Add New". Once there click on the top left on "Upload Plugin".&lt;br&gt;- Once installed you will see "VPN Resellers" appear in the admin menu on the left (as shown below).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%201.png?width=516&amp;amp;height=562&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%201.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 1" width="516" height="562" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 516px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;3. Fill in your API key&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Go to your VPNresellers account page and click on the "VPN Access" tab, or go there by simply clicking on &lt;a href="https://app.vpnresellers.com/api-access"&gt;this link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;On this page you can find your personal API key, go ahead and copy this. Go back to your wordpress site and click on the VPNresellers plugin tab.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paste the API key into the API Token field.&lt;br&gt;Then click on Save Changes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%202.png?width=772&amp;amp;height=289&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%202.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 2" width="772" height="289" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 772px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;After you have done this, your wordpress site is now succesfully connected to your VPNresellers account, meaning that it is able to create and suspend VPN accounts automatically.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;4. Create a VPN product within Woocommerce&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Next is to create the VPN products that you want to sell, most partners would have different offerings such as a Month, 1 year and 2 year package etc. For each different offering a product has to be made. To do this go to "products" and then "add new".&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- At product data select "Simple Subscription"&lt;br&gt;- Mark the "Virtual" checkbox&lt;br&gt;- VPN product? Mark yes&lt;br&gt;- Subscription price is the amount charged per either month or other period you set (can even be per day)&lt;br&gt;- Expire after is when the subscription needs to end. So for example an annual package expires after 12 months.&lt;br&gt;- Singup fee is if you want to charge a one time fee to become customer (not recommended to use, leave it blank)&lt;br&gt;- Free Trial is if you want to offer a free period.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;- Sale price is if you want a special discount price for a specific period (not recommended to use, leave it blank).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%204.png?width=1385&amp;amp;height=583&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%204.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 4" width="1385" height="583" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 1385px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;5. Selling process&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Now you have setup your products, they are available to place on your site, most VPN companies will have a sign up page. You can however also simply offer the package directly. You are free to setup the site as you please.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%205.png?width=1185&amp;amp;height=692&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%205.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 5" width="1185" height="692" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 1185px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%206.png?width=1248&amp;amp;height=976&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%206.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 6" width="1248" height="976" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 1248px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%207.png?width=1078&amp;amp;height=1181&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%207.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 7" width="1078" height="1181" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 1078px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;6. How do customers get their VPN?&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;There are 3 ways the Customer gets their VPN login details, important to know is that as default their email address that they have used to register at your site OR if no registration is filled in at the checkout will be used as their username.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Password gets created for them and can be changed when your customer logs into your wordpress site.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;1. They get the login details on the Thank You page after completing the purchase&lt;br&gt;2. They are emailed automatically the login details&lt;br&gt;3. They can see the username and change the password when they login into your wordpress website.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;As you can see below there is a tab for "VPN Account" where customers can see their username&lt;br&gt;"VPN Server list" gives an overview of all servers and allows for people to download the openVPN config file (for example if they want to use VPN on their router).&lt;br&gt;"Change VPN Password" allows the customer to set their own password.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%208.png?width=1129&amp;amp;height=839&amp;amp;name=Install%20VPNresellers%20guide%208.png" alt="Install VPNresellers guide 8" width="1129" height="839" style="height: auto; max-width: 100%; width: 1129px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;h4&gt;7. How to make your website look good&lt;/h4&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Wordpress/Woocommerce has fantastic templates available to make your site look amazing, we recommend to use either Envato or Woocommerce, see links below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Envato: &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://themeforest.net/category/wordpress?term=woocommerce"&gt;https://themeforest.net/category/wordpress?term=woocommerce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woocommerce site: &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://woocommerce.com/product-category/themes/?categoryIds=1033&amp;amp;collections=theme&amp;amp;page=1"&gt;https://woocommerce.com/product-category/themes/?categoryIds=1033&amp;amp;collections=theme&amp;amp;page=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fwordpress-whitelabel-vpn-integration&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:35:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/wordpress-whitelabel-vpn-integration</guid>
      <dc:date>2023-07-14T14:35:04Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Tips how to sell VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/6-tips-how-to-sell-vpn</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Selling a VPN (Virtual Private Network) can be a challenging task as many people may not be aware of the benefits of using one. However, with the right approach and marketing strategies, you can convince potential customers that a VPN is a valuable investment that can help protect their online privacy and security.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Selling a VPN (Virtual Private Network) can be a challenging task as many people may not be aware of the benefits of using one. However, with the right approach and marketing strategies, you can convince potential customers that a VPN is a valuable investment that can help protect their online privacy and security.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Here are some tips for selling a VPN:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ol&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Emphasize the importance of online privacy and security: Many people are not aware of the risks associated with using the internet without a VPN. Emphasize the fact that using a VPN can help protect their online privacy by encrypting their internet traffic, which prevents hackers, governments, and other third-party entities from monitoring their online activities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Highlight the benefits of using a VPN: A VPN can offer numerous benefits to users. For example, a VPN can help users bypass geo-restrictions and access content that may be unavailable in their region. It can also help users avoid internet throttling, which is when internet service providers (ISPs) slow down the internet speed of certain websites or services. A VPN can also provide users with an additional layer of security when using public Wi-Fi networks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Offer competitive pricing: Many consumers are price-sensitive and will compare different VPN services before making a purchase. Offer competitive pricing and provide different pricing plans to cater to different customer needs. Offering discounts and promotions can also help attract customers and increase sales.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Provide excellent customer service: Providing excellent customer service can help establish a good reputation for your VPN service. Offer multiple channels for customers to reach out to your support team and respond promptly to any customer inquiries or concerns. Providing a user-friendly interface and easy setup process can also improve the customer experience.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Offer a free trial or money-back guarantee: Offering a free trial or a money-back guarantee can help alleviate any concerns potential customers may have about the effectiveness of the VPN service. This can also provide an opportunity to showcase the quality of your VPN service and convince customers to make a purchase.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leverage social media and online advertising: Social media and online advertising can help increase brand awareness and attract potential customers. Use social media platforms such as Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram to engage with customers, share updates and promotions, and respond to customer inquiries. Online advertising, such as Google Ads or Facebook Ads, can also help increase visibility and attract potential customers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ol&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, selling a VPN requires a combination of effective marketing strategies, competitive pricing, and excellent customer service. By emphasizing the benefits of using a VPN, providing competitive pricing, offering excellent customer service, and leveraging social media and online advertising, you can successfully sell a VPN service and help protect your customers' online privacy and security.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2F6-tips-how-to-sell-vpn&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>VPN</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:18:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/6-tips-how-to-sell-vpn</guid>
      <dc:date>2023-05-02T10:18:23Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wireguard Explained</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/wireguard-explained</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WireGuard is a revolutionary new VPN protocol that has been making waves in the cybersecurity world. Its innovative design and advanced security features have made it a popular choice among users and service providers alike. In this article, we'll dive deeper into what makes WireGuard so special and explore its benefits and potential use cases.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;WireGuard is a revolutionary new VPN protocol that has been making waves in the cybersecurity world. Its innovative design and advanced security features have made it a popular choice among users and service providers alike. In this article, we'll dive deeper into what makes WireGuard so special and explore its benefits and potential use cases.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;WireGuard was created in 2016 by Jason A. Donenfeld, a security researcher and developer. He wanted to create a VPN protocol that was fast, secure, and easy to use, unlike other VPN protocols that can be slow and complicated to set up.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;One of the key features of WireGuard is its speed. Unlike other VPN protocols, WireGuard uses a modern and efficient cryptographic protocol called the Noise protocol framework. This protocol is designed to be fast and lightweight, making it ideal for mobile devices and low-powered devices. Additionally, WireGuard's small and efficient codebase means that it can be easily integrated into other software and applications.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;WireGuard's security features are also top-notch. It uses state-of-the-art cryptography algorithms, such as Curve25519 for key exchange, ChaCha20 for encryption, and Poly1305 for message authentication. These algorithms ensure that all data transmitted through a WireGuard tunnel is protected from eavesdropping and tampering.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of WireGuard is its simplicity. Its configuration is based on simple and concise text files, which makes it easy to set up and manage. Additionally, WireGuard is designed to work seamlessly with network address translation (NAT), which means that it can operate without the need for complex routing or port forwarding.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;WireGuard's simplicity and efficiency also make it well-suited for embedded systems, such as routers or IoT devices. Its small size and minimal dependencies make it easy to integrate into existing software stacks, and its simplicity and efficiency make it a good fit for resource-constrained environments.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;WireGuard has gained popularity among VPN service providers due to its simplicity and efficiency, as well as its security and speed. Its ease of use and low overhead make it a good choice for users who are looking for a fast and reliable VPN solution that is easy to set up and manage.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;WireGuard has many potential use cases, from protecting personal privacy and security to enabling remote access to business networks. For example, a person who wants to protect their online privacy and security might use WireGuard to connect to a VPN server that is located in a different country. This would allow them to access websites and online services that might be restricted or censored in their home country.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, businesses can use WireGuard to connect remote employees to their network securely and efficiently. WireGuard's lightweight design and streamlined codebase make it well-suited for use in embedded systems, which means that it can be used in a wide range of devices, from routers to IoT devices.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;In summary, WireGuard is a modern and efficient VPN protocol that offers several advantages over other VPN solutions. Its simplicity, speed, and security make it a good fit for a wide range of applications, from embedded systems to cloud-based VPN services. As more users and service providers adopt WireGuard, we can expect to see it become an increasingly popular choice for VPN users and administrators alike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;VPNresellers uses Wiregaurd as its default protocol for all the applications because it has proven to work the best for both speed and security.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fwireguard-explained&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>VPN</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:46:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/wireguard-explained</guid>
      <dc:date>2023-05-02T09:46:07Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making money with VPN services</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/making-money-with-vpn-services</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this digital era, people are searching extra ways on how to earn money online. The reason is quite simple, earning online means that you decide what hours you dedicate to making money. Also there is no limit to how much you can earn online by offering your services. Here arises the question:&amp;nbsp; What are those services that helps you to earn a decent amount of money ? Well, I can say in advance there are many services in the marketing to offer but the one we are putting under spotlight is VPN (Virtual Private Network).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In this digital era, people are searching extra ways on how to earn money online. The reason is quite simple, earning online means that you decide what hours you dedicate to making money. Also there is no limit to how much you can earn online by offering your services. Here arises the question:&amp;nbsp; What are those services that helps you to earn a decent amount of money ? Well, I can say in advance there are many services in the marketing to offer but the one we are putting under spotlight is VPN (Virtual Private Network).&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;VPN’s are quickly gaining popularity in many countries as people are more aware about their online security and privacy, considering it more crucial. &amp;nbsp;While using the Internet, you can never know if someone is snooping your data, especially when accessing public Wi-Fi hotspots which are usually unprotected and not secure. A VPN helps you do your online browsing and transactions through a secure encrypted tunnel, so no one can have access to your data. With no doubt, it is a wise decision to choose such emerging business to offer as part of your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;There are tons of services throughout the world that offer VPN services, however, you need to look at the bigger picture when choosing a VPN provider to resell it to your customers such as, Price and quality, speed, privacy,&amp;nbsp; reliability and customer support.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESELLING&amp;nbsp; A “VPN”:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;if you don’t have enough capital&amp;nbsp; to buy a large portion of bandwidth or technical knowledge to build your own, you can partner up with reselling companies that offer the product and all technical resources you need in order to sell.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Reselling means that you would use the existing infrastructure of a well-known provider and set your own price and plans. You may go for reselling if you have identified a niche but does not have enough technical expertise to create or own product or rather focus on only selling it.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FIND A PROVIDER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;There is variety of&amp;nbsp; choices pricing option when you dive into a VPN reselling market. Your choice solely depends on what network specs you want and how much you can rely on your provider ability to overcome any possible issues you or your customers may face .&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SETTING SUITABLE PRICE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The price you put on your service is going to be highly dependent on the price you’re paying for provision in the first place but make sure you’re at least competitive with other resellers.&amp;nbsp;Offering a featured service might help attracting more customers.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRANDING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Your brand is your business.&amp;nbsp; We will provide the white label software for free or we offer a rebrand service, where we will rebrand it with your own logo, color and style at competitive market price. Custom branding allows you to create awareness of your brand in the market and increase loyalty and credibility. It also distinguish you from the competition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AFFILIATE PROGRAMS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Word “affiliate”&amp;nbsp; is very familiar and you may quickly associate that with the ability to make extra money. Affiliate programs do offer those opportunities and being a VPN affiliate can be lucrative.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the most common paths to affiliate marketing success:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CREATING AN AFFILIATE REVIEW SITE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Affiliate review sites are one of the most common pathways to success. This style of site is dedicated to reviewing different products or services in a certain niche. Setting up an affiliate site might be a great idea ko kickstart your VPN business .&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SELLING AFFILIATE PRODUCTS VIA EMAIL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Email marketing is a great way to drive traffic to an affiliate offer. By building an email list of people in a certain niche, you can recommend them products they might be interested.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADD LINKS TO YOUR WEBSITE OR BLOG:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you’re not completely focused on affiliate marketing, but would like to add some additional income to your online efforts, then you can include affiliate links wherever they make sense. This could be done through a link on your social media profiles or stories, on a separate resource page on your website,&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECIDING THE BEST OPTION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Both &lt;a href="https://www.vpnresellers.com/vpn-reseller"&gt;VPN white label programs&lt;/a&gt; and affiliate programs have their own merits and limitations.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The choice entirely depends on your clients needs and how much effort, time and capital you are willing to put into this business.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;White Label program is better suited to those who have enough time and resources to make it a success. If you are looking for branding yourself reseller program is suitable for you and it generates a continuous source of income.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you are already having your own business or run some popular blogs, you might go for affiliate programs&amp;nbsp; and simply direct clients to providers thus generating the side income.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you need to know more about the perks of our white label program, get in touch with us.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fmaking-money-with-vpn-services&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Getting started</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 17:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/making-money-with-vpn-services</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-06-21T17:06:07Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to sell VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/how-to-sell-vpn</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to sell VPN and more of it is probably the most asked question our partners ask us. After all building a scalable business is dependant on growth. I've been in Sales in the SAAS space for over 15 years and I'd like to share some tips to help you grow your business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you are concerned about your online privacy,&amp;nbsp; want to safeguard your data from third parties, or are considering&amp;nbsp; a way to dodge geo-restrictions, a VPN might help you to cover them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;How to sell VPN and more of it is probably the most asked question our partners ask us. After all building a scalable business is dependant on growth. I've been in Sales in the SAAS space for over 15 years and I'd like to share some tips to help you grow your business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you are concerned about your online privacy,&amp;nbsp; want to safeguard your data from third parties, or are considering&amp;nbsp; a way to dodge geo-restrictions, a VPN might help you to cover them.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY YOU NEED A VPN:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;One of the greatest benefit of using VPN is data protection. Since so much of our lives are online today, security has become a major concern.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;VPN not only protects your online activities and personal information but also it adds an extra security layer against cybercriminals particularly if you regularly access the public networks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;A VPN creates a secure tunnel thus allowing you to keep your private data safe from malicious actors.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IS VPN WORTH PAYING:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you can relate to any of the aforementioned scenarios, One thing is for sure that you need a good VPN. As far as this question is concerned , then the answer is YES , a VPN is worth buying. Why not, when you can have all those advantages of a VPN by paying just a few dollars per month?&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE VPN’s : A NIGHTMARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;“Free” isn’t free when it comes to free VPN’s. using free VPN’s is just like protecting your privacy at the expense of your own privacy. These services actually allow malicious third parties to sneak through your personal data and much more. VPN’s are meant to protect you from all these malicious activities, so it’s better to pay some amount rather than compromising your privacy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SELLING A VPN: A VPN RESELLER PROGRAM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;One can boost up the revenues by selling VPN using VPN reselling program , which is designed to offer internet/digital marketers the opportunity to sell VPN services provided by another company. They provide the marketer with all back-end tools and server’s access.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This program gives an excellent opportunity to resell VPN services to the customers and being a VPN reseller you may buy services at discounted prices.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Here’s some key points and guide to a VPN reseller program:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Picking your tech stack setup:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Some of the main things you need to have are VPN reseller provider. You can sign up here, account management and billing software such as&amp;nbsp; WHMCS. If you don’t want WHMCS you might go for other options such as Wordpress or Hostbill.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connecting account and billing software with VPNresellers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;After you have made your choice , the next step is to connect your system with VPNresellers.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Setting a best suited price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The price you set for your service will in the first place be highly dependent on the price you pay for marketing your service. In addition you must ensure that you are at least competitive with other VPN providers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Branding&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Sell the services under your brand name as white-label service provider.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU CAN DO AS A VPN RESELLER?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Sell VPN directly on your own website&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Directly purchase VPN services from your credit balance&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Manage your accounts in the VPNReseller dashboard&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Automatic renewal option&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Monthly price of VPN depends on how many active accounts you have&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHY RESELL VPN’s:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The VPN market is at the top of its game now and user as well as business privacy concerns are bigger than ever. Before, VPNs were mostly used among companies and universities for the sole ability to access private data and resources. Now, VPN services are an everyday thing, used by Internet users all around the globe. Data leaks, Internet restrictions, privacy-unfriendly laws are just a few reasons as to why the VPN market has skyrocketed and will continue to grow. VPN resells are increasing too, as many want to jump on the train and take advantage of the growing VPN service provider market.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UNDERSTANDING VPN PROTOCOLS&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;VPN protocols are designed with the sole purpose of facilitating the encapsulation and encryption of data transmitting via network.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;As a VPN reseller, it would help to understand the different VPN protocols. Among many different types there are few that are commonly used.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point to point tunneling protocol (PPTP):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This protocol encapsulates and encrypt data using IP header and it can be used for both remote-access and site to site VPN connections.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layer 2 Tunneling Protocol:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Cisco developed this protocol and it uses elements of PPTP and layer 2 Forwarding. It combines the aspects of both technologies in single protocol and adds an extra layer of security at transport level.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Socket Tunneling protocols (SSTP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This is one of the latest technology that has that has advantage of getting through firewalls and web proxies that have been known to block PPTP and L2TP. The encapsulation is done using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) channel on HTTPS protocol.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FINDING A VPN RESELLER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a company that offers quality VPN services, VPNresellers&amp;nbsp;has everything you need. We also have quality back end tools that can help to manage every aspect of your business.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;VPNresellers has a solid VPN reseller program that will give you everything you need to make money. We also have competitive commissions to help you make a profit on every sale.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you want to find out how can we help you become a successful VPN reseller. Sign up below&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fhow-to-sell-vpn&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Getting started</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:34:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/how-to-sell-vpn</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-06-16T19:34:39Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitelabel Iphone App now live</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/whitelabel-iphone-app-now-live</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are super proud to be able to announce that as of today we are live in the Apple App store, from now on IOS users no longer have to resort to manual setup. Instead simply download the app, login and use VPN!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We are super proud to be able to announce that as of today we are live in the Apple App store, from now on IOS users no longer have to resort to manual setup. Instead simply download the app, login and use VPN!&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This app is free to use for all our partners and now support a full range of Windows, Mac, Android Mobile, Android/Firestick TV and now finally IOS.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The IOS app is also available for the custom branding service. We are dedicated to continue innovating and improving all apps for our partners. Your customer clients will automatically update without costing you any time.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;We are excited to see how we can grow even faster together.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/IMG_2548%20(1).jpg?width=170&amp;amp;name=IMG_2548%20(1).jpg" alt="IMG_2548 (1)" width="170" style="width: 170px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/IMG_2549.jpg?width=170&amp;amp;name=IMG_2549.jpg" alt="IMG_2549" width="170" style="width: 170px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Direct link to app store:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://h2.t.hubspotemail.net/e2t/c/*N2RT2mhwDKm7N6_6zfq-13SC0/*W27WBQD7F2GsvW3FTLNf6Q2g2_0/5/f18dQhb0S5fl8YHsJYW7B8djN6ghkRDVWs4R056ZJlzW5r8vwP3mm42mMQznpS31RfzN6YHzwYCf2WmW7djyB27vcmDYW7v7blF6BrqyWW24SS1z1Q45jcW1-W6_91vkg-SW1rfS4-3cLyGJW5KxXB65KDCtZW12tL7f5B4Lq6W7r74zS1FpGlpVr3y2623Gh7kW3bPyFL3CblxqW5RlSdT5xNCj8W8mGgzn313MJ5W5nNHMD3pDS77W8gGglS5KY1FtN8Mhy0M-xxFzW3z1_x-5w6y4zW3zwnD25hfRnFW38m__d8yxSwVW34qz2f3YkzfjW8qGJv13nLdHsW5Qv5Yq3VTBrtW5hlHxz3pjZ-gW3K1nBD5G4JbsW8fLXDC1BgLlTW7kJ19h73R1h2W224m2Z22Td_QW80mGf26bT-F9W1tcl0r8lC5ZWW1wRS6N5cNxtyVBrr0H7VHnGVW3x2hPw6fT1G5W4DbD_27Y72YYN5104X-rVprCW56gBW-8qwDKLf2x86cq04"&gt;https://apps.apple.com/app/id1506797696&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;All VPNresellers apps:&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://h2.t.hubspotemail.net/e2t/c/*N2RT2mhwDKm7N6_6zfq-13SC0/*W8jC7df7r81x8W44vtg32Lqyl00/5/f18dQhb0S5fy8XJ8yvW7B8djN6ghkRDVWs4R057JG4vW5r8vwP3mm44rN5y5LmVQbpJ3VRJWCR5_MPY7N1nPLDM5ZX7pW1V0Q104c2zn2W4cQldQ7KWq4GW54WsLk2MTPSyVKng6q1Wg4bjW76NPgj7vHlczW61WJ7_2N33B5W3_t0gL32Gf2QW4cBzLv49z-4PN2MV0XLbl_WLW7z2NMJ7vRb97W30T_rP2Vv3csW1G8Mxx1Bb4rMW7R8s_17q7lz4W8P7_3k7t5cFNW53TJ_R2Rk5WGN1JSWjFnDTMcN1M7j2nq0NTXW4hqnlj4n6nhQW6nbBpY55TCnqW1YYK7_7t58S8Vv34rz1BqPXjW8XTkhD2KBK-xW1zLkYs7qC_vBN4c_vsn9zM7DW3T03vy8csGDVVD2JBL7gYnvwW5D4WXP2_0vgWW5lNtg25z012sV10Nbd5x6CKZW70zlJX1_MQW2W7xNvbR67mWcmW5blq_W1NhbTbW1PDlDq2dpqD7McTSRKcSG7rf5F8v0t02"&gt;https://www.vpnresellers.com/vpn-whitelabel-software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fwhitelabel-iphone-app-now-live&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>VPN</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 22:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/whitelabel-iphone-app-now-live</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-04-23T22:07:53Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Corona virus is a huge chance for selling more VPN</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/how-corona-virus-is-a-huge-chance-for-selling-more-vpn</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Due to widespread fears over CoronaVirus, entire organisations have gone from a traditional office setting to scrambling for a plan to provide secure remote access. As&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;confirmed coronavirus cases increase&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;across the globe, organisations are having employees work from home in an effort to decrease the virus's spread. From&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;small businesses&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;all the way to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;tech giants&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;like Facebook, Amazon, Google, and Microsoft, companies are now requiring most (if not all) of their workforce to telecommute through at least the end of March.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Due to widespread fears over CoronaVirus, entire organisations have gone from a traditional office setting to scrambling for a plan to provide secure remote access. As&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;confirmed coronavirus cases increase&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;across the globe, organisations are having employees work from home in an effort to decrease the virus's spread. From&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;small businesses&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;all the way to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;tech giants&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;like Facebook, Amazon, Google, and Microsoft, companies are now requiring most (if not all) of their workforce to telecommute through at least the end of March.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;h2&gt;Take advantage of the corona virus surge for VPN's&lt;/h2&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;According to a&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;study&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;OpenVPN conducted in 2019, 24% of companies haven’t updated its remote work security policy in over a year, and 44% say its IT department did not lead the remote work security policy plan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So what can your organisation do now in light of this situation?&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Here are some questions outlined that your customers are asking themselves during this time.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ol&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;What's the maximum number of users who need remote access?&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How does this translate into additional bandwidth needed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How soon will we need additional bandwidth?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How quickly can additional bandwidth be provided?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How quickly can we obtain additional licenses and other resources?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How much more will it cost for additional bandwidth and network?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;What technologies can we use to boost bandwidth cost-effectively?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How will cybersecurity threats be handled in such a situation?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How do we secure and protect the increased amount of data traffic?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;How do we scale back once the demand for remote access has returned to normal levels?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;What resources are available from local access carriers?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="col-11"&gt;What resources are available from WAN carriers and internet service providers (ISPs)?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ol&gt; 
&lt;h2&gt;VPN: An essential tool for remote work&lt;/h2&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Securing remote access to internal systems and online services is typically achieved by using a&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Virtual Private Network&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;(VPN). In the case of CoronaVirus — many people have turned to VPNs for help.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VPN provides your business with a securely encrypted connection to the network over the public internet. It provides an important piece of layered security that's essential for data protection. Using a VPN gives you the ability to remotely access important network resources and connect your company's branches and locations worldwide. This is extremely important during pandemics (and even just during flu season) when working remotely is the only choice.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;We have seen a huge surge in our partners selling more VPN's. If you haven't already taken advantage now would be the time to go to market!&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fhow-corona-virus-is-a-huge-chance-for-selling-more-vpn&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>VPN</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 15:22:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/how-corona-virus-is-a-huge-chance-for-selling-more-vpn</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-03-17T15:22:31Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native VPN Integration with HostBill is now live</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/native-vpn-integration-with-hostbill-is-now-live</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are super excited to report that we are now natively integrated with hostbillapp.com! HostBill is a self-funded, privately owned company based in Poland. They have helped over 2000 companies around the globe from various industries to build their brands on top of a stable billing, automation, support and client management solution that &lt;a href="https://hostbillapp.com/"&gt;HostBill&lt;/a&gt; provides.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We are super excited to report that we are now natively integrated with hostbillapp.com! HostBill is a self-funded, privately owned company based in Poland. They have helped over 2000 companies around the globe from various industries to build their brands on top of a stable billing, automation, support and client management solution that &lt;a href="https://hostbillapp.com/"&gt;HostBill&lt;/a&gt; provides.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With HostBill accounts are created and managed automatically. Automation also handles billing and invoicing operations. Clients can view their VPN and billing details in our user-friendly client panel, and admins can manage accounts from admin area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/hostbillapp%201.png?width=1024&amp;amp;name=hostbillapp%201.png" alt="hostbillapp 1" width="1024" style="width: 1024px;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.vpnresellers.com/hs-fs/hubfs/hostbillapp%202.png?width=1024&amp;amp;name=hostbillapp%202.png" alt="hostbillapp 2" width="1024" style="width: 1024px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;VPN Resellers module for HostBill gives you an excellent opportunity to effortlessly start your VPN reselling business and build a new source of recurring revenue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;With HostBill accounts are created and managed automatically. Automation also handles billing and invoicing operations. Clients can view their VPN and billing details in our user-friendly client panel, and admins can manage accounts from the admin area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to set it up, visit &lt;a href="https://hostbill.atlassian.net/wiki/spaces/DOCS/pages/926875661/VPNReseller"&gt;this link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fnative-vpn-integration-with-hostbill-is-now-live&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Getting started</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 19:34:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/native-vpn-integration-with-hostbill-is-now-live</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-03-16T19:34:57Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap VPN reseller overview</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/cheap-vpn-reseller-overview</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of our first time website visitors are researching for the best cheap VPN reseller program in the market. There are plenty of VPN companies, most of them very bad and a few giants who are great but have their own downsides. All in all it is a challenge and therefore we decided to create this overview.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Most of our first time website visitors are researching for the best cheap VPN reseller program in the market. There are plenty of VPN companies, most of them very bad and a few giants who are great but have their own downsides. All in all it is a challenge and therefore we decided to create this overview.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;Lets start off with a few ground rules to define "cheap" as we probably don't want to do business with some guy in a basement and a home computer setup to run his VPN business on. That might be "cheap" but isn't what you probably want in a partner for a whole list of reasons.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;What we need is:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Good and reliable technology (both software and hardware)&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;No limits or other factors that will give people the feeling of being cheated&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Supporting the most popular devices&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Work on Mobile, Laptop, Desktop and smart TV&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Allow P2P&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Plenty of global locations&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;No logs&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Alright, so taking that into account, we can look at the market. What you will find that the majority of VPN companies will offer a reseller program. When people speak about reselling VPN, they either mean to actually resell a brand or they want to offer VPN under their own brand. When you sell under your own name it is called Whitelabel.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Some companies offer only Whitelabel reselling (that is us) , some only offer reseller programs and others both. When you are reselling a brand, the advantage is that with some of them it is a brand name that people might know and trust. Although if you were to ask your family to name 3 VPN companies i'm pretty confident they will not be able to.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;A big brand usually has good servers and service, but how do you know what the top ones are? Well let us tell you, the biggest globally are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. ExpressVPN&lt;br&gt;2. NordVPN&lt;br&gt;3. Hide.me&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Don't even bother with the rest, seriously.... it is most likely not worth your time nor should you want to be reselling it. Do you really want to risk upsetting your audience / referrals? We would recommend to visit their websites research the conditions for reselling. It will differ for each and changes overtime.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Now that been said, there are a couple of huge disadvantages or reselling a brand's product.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Your offering is no different from anyone else, you cannot differentiate, which makes competing hard.&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Customers are not your customers&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Your % of the profit is usually low when you are small, only when you would have a big volume of resells will your cut grow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;These are the primary reasons why selling VPN through Whitelabel is becoming more popular. Some of the challenges with finding a whitelabel solution is usually that it costs quite a bit upfront to get started. As most of the VPN companies that offer this, usually want to attract other bigger businesses and websites. Now nothing wrong with that, but what if your a smaller business? &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;We wanted to take away any of the roadblocks that companies face to not go Whitelabel. So with us there is:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- No signup fee&lt;br&gt;- Cheapest in the market with $1,99 , competitors usually are around $4 but sometimes far more.&lt;br&gt;- Credit system for only pay as you go (only pay when you have actual sold customers)&lt;br&gt;- Credit never expires&lt;br&gt;- Credit gets charged daily so that you can be super flexible with renewing or cancelling at anytime.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;- Free to use Whitelabel software&lt;br&gt;- Rebranding to your own brand possible&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Click on &lt;a href="https://www.vpnresellers.com/vpn-reseller"&gt;VPN reseller&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about it.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fcheap-vpn-reseller-overview&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>VPN</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 09:50:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/cheap-vpn-reseller-overview</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-03-05T09:50:38Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes the best vpn reseller program?</title>
      <link>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/what-makes-the-best-vpn-reseller-program</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a variety of factors that makes "the best VPN reseller program". In this post will try to remove any subjective points, not simply preach how fantastic we are, but instead focus on objectively looking at the market. With the goal to hopefully help you make the right choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;There is a variety of factors that makes "the best VPN reseller program". In this post will try to remove any subjective points, not simply preach how fantastic we are, but instead focus on objectively looking at the market. With the goal to hopefully help you make the right choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pricing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;When your reselling a product, the markup margin is of vital essence to determine if a program is "good" or "bad". As you have to sell the product you'll have costs for marketing, sales and in most cases some level of support. This does not mean you are the one fixing issues, but since they are your customers it is only logical a customer approaches you first. To build a strong recurring revenue stream it is recommend to not sell 1 off's but instead focus on a service that has recurring revenue each month. What you will find is that retaining customers is far easier then acquiring new ones. This way you can build a scalable business that has dependable revenue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;We looked at the top 10 &lt;a href="https://www.vpnresellers.com/vpn-reseller"&gt;VPN reseller&lt;/a&gt; programs and found that it ranges from $2 dollars per VPN a month to the most extreme of a company that asks a setup fee of $10.000,- (so that is before you have sold a single VPN). So before you choose your partner, review a couple options.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whitelabel or no whitelabel?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;When reselling your either selling someone's brand or using your own brand. Not all reseller programs have the possibility for getting the service in whitelabel format. Selling under your own brand has the huge advantage that customers truly do business with you. Otherwise they know your just the in-between party that might not really be necessary and will have reduced loyalty to your business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Also what we have seen is that just reselling will give you typically a 25% profit margin, while with whitelabel it is usually around 75% margin that you can make.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;State of the art technology supporting the most used systems.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;As you are selling, you don't want headaches of software en servers that do not work. VPN is a tricky business, for example Netflix makes it it's mission to try and block anyone who uses VPN from using Netflix. Any VPN provider has to deal with those type of issues. The technology and experience the company has is therefore vital. Our recommendation would be to go for a partner that has been in the hosting business for a long time.&amp;nbsp; Plus look at third party reviews, such as on the WHMCS marketplace. If a company has no reviews or negative reviews it is telling that their customer base is either tiny or nobody felt good enough about their services to leave a review.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dedicated Account Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;You might be new to selling VPN and there will always be plenty of questions that need answers. It is therefore a huge benefit if there is 1 person connected to your account that knows you and has your interest at heart. The skillset of this person should be a mixture of Sales &amp;amp; Marketing expertise. As this is the main thing that needs to happen for a Sale to take place.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Training for new partners by jointly developing a marketing plan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;As an entrepreneur you learn through failures, it often helps tough if you can throw your ideas safely at a partner with experience that can help you improve your plan. A true partner is in it all in the way!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consult and assist in the technology stack to sell efficiently and effectively.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Having the right setup can make or break a business. When your dealing with a partner they should have the experience to know what works well and why. Technology is ever changing and modern businesses need to adapt to be best equipped to enter the arena of selling VPN.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  
&lt;img src="https://track.hubspot.com/__ptq.gif?a=532220&amp;amp;k=14&amp;amp;r=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.vpnresellers.com%2Fblog%2Fwhat-makes-the-best-vpn-reseller-program&amp;amp;bu=https%253A%252F%252Fwww.vpnresellers.com%252Fblog&amp;amp;bvt=rss" alt="" width="1" height="1" style="min-height:1px!important;width:1px!important;border-width:0!important;margin-top:0!important;margin-bottom:0!important;margin-right:0!important;margin-left:0!important;padding-top:0!important;padding-bottom:0!important;padding-right:0!important;padding-left:0!important; "&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Getting started</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.vpnresellers.com/blog/what-makes-the-best-vpn-reseller-program</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-02-06T09:04:24Z</dc:date>
      <dc:creator>Nick Snow</dc:creator>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
